https://www.kleenline.com/privacy/

Please see ProMach's Official Coronavirus (COVID-19) update.
Disclaimer & Privacy Policy
HomeDisclaimer & Privacy Policy
Benchmark Automation LLC Disclaimer
This page may contain other proprietary notices and copyright information, the terms of which must be observed and followed. INFORMATION ON THIS WEB SITE IS PROVIDED "AS IS" WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND, EITHER EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, THE IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE, OR NON-INFRINGEMENT. SOME JURISDICTIONS DO NOT ALLOW THE EXCLUSION OF IMPLIED WARRANTIES, SO THE ABOVE EXCLUSION MAY NOT APPLY TO YOU.
Information on this web site may contain technical inaccuracies or typographical errors. Information may be changed or updated without notice. Benchmark Automation LLC may also make improvements and/or changes in the products and/or the programs described in this information at any time without notice.
Benchmark Automation LLC does not want to receive confidential or proprietary information from you through our web site. Please note that any information or material sent to Benchmark Automation LLC will be deemed NOT to be confidential. By sending Benchmark Automation LLC any information or material, you grant Benchmark Automation LLC an unrestricted, irrevocable license to use, reproduce, display, perform, modify, transmit and distribute those materials or information, and you also agree that Benchmark Automation LLC is free to use any ideas, concepts, know-how or techniques that you send us for any purpose.
Information Benchmark Automation LLC publishes on the World Wide Web may contain references or cross references to other products, programs and services that are not announced or available in your country. Such references do not imply that Benchmark Automation LLC intends to announce such products, programs or services in your country. Consult a Benchmark Automation LLC representative for information regarding the products, programs and services which may be available to you.
Benchmark Automation LLC makes no representations whatsoever about any other web site which you may access through this one. When you access a non-Benchmark Automation LLC web site, please understand that it is independent from Benchmark Automation LLC and that Benchmark Automation LLC has no control over the content on that web site. In addition, a link to a non-Benchmark Automation LLC web site does not mean that Benchmark Automation LLC endorses or accepts any responsibility for the content, or the use, of such web site. It is up to you to take precautions to ensure that whatever you select for your use is free of such items as viruses, worms, trojan horses and other items of a destructive nature.
IN NO EVENT WILL BENCHMARK AUTOMATION LLC BE LIABLE TO ANY PARTY FOR ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT, SPECIAL OR OTHER CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES FOR ANY USE OF THIS WEBSITE, OR ON ANY OTHER HYPERLINKED WEBSITE, INCLUDING, WITHOUT LIMITATION, ANY LOST PROFITS, BUSINESS INTERRUPTION, LOSS OF PROGRAMS OR OTHER DATA ON YOUR INFORMATION HANDLING SYSTEM OR OTHERWISE, EVEN IF WE ARE EXPRESSLY ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES.
Furthermore, all information contained within this website is the property of Benchmark Automation LLC Copyright 2020.
Benchmark Automation LLC Privacy Policy
The information we learn from customers helps us personalize and continually improve your experience at kleenline.com. Here are the types of information we gather.
Information You Give Us: We receive and store any information you enter on our Web site or give us in any other way. We do not sell or rent your personal information to others without your consent. We use the information we collect only for the purposes of sending promotional information, enhancing the operation of our site, serving advertisements, for statistical purposes and to administer our systems. We DO NOT use third parties to provide customer service, to serve site content, to serve the advertisements you see on our site, to conduct surveys, to help administer promotional emails, or to administer drawings or contests, but reserve the right to do so in the future without advance notice. Our computer system protects personal information using advanced firewall technology.
Information from Other Sources: For reasons such as improving personalization of our service, we might receive information about you from other sources and add it to our account information.
